revtwt.com 2015-12-25

# RevTwt - Twitter Advertising - Make money from your tweets!Twitter Advertising Network

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
_This statement was last updated May 1, 2009._

**1\. Collecting your Personal Information**  
The information we collect from you is only for the purpose of providing the services of this website. Personal information we collect from you is limited to your email address and Twitter account information for the purpose of posting ads using APIs.

**2\. Use of your Personal Information**  
We use your personal information for two primary purposes: 

  * To identify your account in RevTwt and to make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once. 
  * To enable us to carry out the functions of this website. 

RevTwt will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on RevTwt or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of RevTwt, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of RevTwt, its Web site, or the public.

**3\. Control of your Personal Information**  
When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, RevTwt will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

**4\. Security of your Personal Information**  
RevTwt strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. In the case of Twitter accounts which information both RevTwt and Twitter has, RevTwt may cooperate with Twitter to identify spammers. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where RevTwt, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password, so do not share these with others.

**5\. Use of Cookies**  
Cookies will be placed on your computer by RevTwt only for login and gameplay purposes. Cookies will never be placed on your computer by third parties. A cookie must be set to keep you logged into your account by holding account information that is essential for the login process.

**6\. Changes to this Statement**  
RevTwt will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. 

**7\. Contact Information**  
RevTwt welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, please contact us by [ **e-mail**](http://revtwt.com/common/contact.php).
